Guide to the Nadine P. Winter Council of the District of Columbia papers, Circa 1976-1990 MS2188
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Political correspondence with or concerning institutions and issues, 1976-1990; Series 4
  Organized into two subseries: Institutions and Issues and events.
  - Institutions, 1976-1990; Series 4 Subseries 1
    - 8th St. Associates, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - 18th & Columbia Rd. Bus Ass., 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - ACORN, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Adelante Advocacy Center, Inc., 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Robert A. Ades & Associates, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Advocates for Older People, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - African American Legal Defense, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - African Heritage Center, 1985; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - African American Holiday Association, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Afro-American Newspapers, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Alan Williams and Associates, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - All Souls Church, Unitarian, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Allen Ame Church, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Alpha Kappa Alpha, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Ambassador Baptist Church, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - American Association of Retired Persons, 1987-1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - America Business Women Association, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - American Cancer Society, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, 1986-1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - American College of OBGYN, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - American Committee on Africa, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - American Committee on Africa, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - American Federation of Government Employees, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - American Heart Association, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - American Institute of Architects, 1986-1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - American Jewish Congress, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - American Lung Association of Northern Virginia, 1987-1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - American Magazine, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - American Muslims' Convention, 1985; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - American Petroleum Institute, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - American Red Cross, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - American Security Bank, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Americans for Democratic Action, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - Anacostia Bible Church, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - Anacostia Garden Club, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 35)
    - Anacostia Library, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 36)
    - Andrew Cacho Drummers and Dancers, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 37)
    - Anti-Defamation League, 1989-1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 38)
    - Apartment and Office Building Association, 1989-1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 39)
    - Amnesty International, 1986-1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 40)
    - AR Plumley and Company, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 41)
    - Asian Pacific American Chamber of Commerce, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 66, Folder 42)
    - Associated Catholic Charities, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Barney Circle Freeway Modification, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Bay Street Block Club, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - The Bible Way Church, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Bicentennial Black History Committee, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Black Women's Agenda Inc, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Blue Cross/Blue Sheild, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Blue Plains Environmental Research Center, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Bragg, Emmett, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Brown Memorial Ame Church, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Business Organized to Help, Inc, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - C&P Telephone, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Calvary Episcopal Church, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Calvary Shelter Inc, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Capital Area Community Food Bank, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - The Capital Club, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Capital Evening Cure, Inc, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Capital View Baptist Church, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Capitol Hill Arts Workshop, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Capitol Hill Association of Merchants and Professionals, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Capitol Hill Broker's Association, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Capitol Hill Children's Museum, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Capitol Hill code Enforcement Coalition, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Capitol Hill East/West Condominium Association, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Capitol Hill Homemaker and Health Services, Inc, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Capitol Hill Hospital, 1989-1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Capitol Hill Pregnancy Crisis Center, 1985; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Capitol Hill Seventh Day Adventist Church, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Capitol Hill Taxpayers Alliance, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - Capitol Hill Towers, 1989-1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - Capitol Hill Traffic Task Force, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 31)
    - Capitol House Condominiums, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 32)
    - Catholic University of America, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 33)
    - Center for Dispute Settlement, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 34)
    - Center for Youth Services, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 35)
    - Chartered Health Plan, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 67, Folder 36)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Chevy Chase Citizens Association, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Children's Hospital National Medical Center and National Research Equitable Tax Relief, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Church's Freedom, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Cianbro Corporation and Hull, Inc., 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Church Association for Community Service, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - CITICORP, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Citizens United for Rehab, of Errants, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Civic Dept. Ass., 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Clevelanf Park Historical Society, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - The Coalition for Cultural Equality, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Committee for the Preservation of Langston Golf Course, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Committee of One Hundred Ministers, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Committee on 100 on the Federal City, 1985; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Community Development Federal Credit Union, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Community Family Life Services, Inc, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Community Level Education On Aids and Narcotics, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - The Community Monitors of Washington, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Community Workers of America Local 2336, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Congress Heights Community Association, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Congressional Cemetary, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Consortium of Academic Health Science Centers, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Contex Inc., 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Consumer Utility Board, 1985; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Consumer Utility News, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Convention Center, 1976-1977; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Convention Center, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Corporate Communications/B and O Railroad/CSX Corporation, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - Corporation Against Drug Abuse, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - Council for Court Excellence, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - C&P Telephone Company, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - Craston Public Finance Report, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 32)
    - Creative Associates, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 33)
    - Creative Enterprises, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 34)
    - Crime Stoppers Club, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 35)
    - CSX Corporation, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 36)
    - CSX Reality, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 37)
    - CYS Center for Youth Services, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 38)
    - D'Arc Jeanne, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 39)
    - Dankers Restaurant, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 40)
    - Dart Drug, Inc., 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 41)
    - Data Spectrum, Inc., 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 42)
    - James Davis Advertising and Design, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 43)
    - Democratic Socialists of America, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 44)
    - D.C. Association of Deaf Citizens, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 45)
    - DC Association of Retired Citizens, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 46)
    - District of Columbia Association of School Psychologists, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 68, Folder 47)
    - DC Bicycle Advisory Council, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - DC Builders Association, 1984; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - DC Bankers' Association, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - DCBA/CIIC, 1984; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - DC Building Industry Association, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - DC Coalition for Justice, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - District of Columbia Chamber of Commerce, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - DC Committee to Promote Washington, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - DC Common Cause, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - DC Consortium of Academic Health Science Centers, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - DC Cure, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - DC Democratic Women's Club, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - DC Federation of Civic Association, Inc., 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - DC General Hospital, 1988-1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - DC General Hospital, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - DC Good Neighbors, Inc, 1984; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - DC Government Hispanic Employees Association, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - DC Historic Preservation Review Board, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - DC Housing Finance Agency, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - District of Columbia Hospital Assoc., 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - DC Metropolitan Subcontractors Association, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - DC Preservation League, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - District of Columbia Pretrial Services Agency, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - DC Private Industry Council Inc., 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - DC PTA, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - DC Retirement Board, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - District of Columbia Society of internal Medicine, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - DC Street Academy Inc, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - DC Tax Amnesty, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - DC Taxicab Commission, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - DC united Way, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - DC Urban Homesteading Program, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - DC Wine & Spirits Wholesalers Association, Inc., 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Delmarva Foundation for Medical Care, Inc., 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Disadvantage Women-Owned Business interprise Program, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Diversified Resources Incorporated, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Douglas Memorial Methodist, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - The Doug Williams Foundation, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Downtown Partnership, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Duke Ellington School of the Arts, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Drivers, Chauffers and Helpers local Union 639, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - DRM & Associates Inc, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Earth Day Committee, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - East of the River Community Art Program, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 25)
    - Eastern Striders, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 26)
    - Ebeneezer United Methodist Church, 1985; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 27)
    - Ebenezer United Methodist Church, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 28)
    - Education in Partnership with Technology, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 29)
    - Edward C. Mazique Parent Child Center, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 30)
    - Edwards & Wiggins Investment Group, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 31)
    - Electronic Funds Alternative Program, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 32)
    - Emmanual Baptist Chruch, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 33)
    - Fairlawn Citizens Association, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 34)
    - The Fairlawn Coalition, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 35)
    - Faith bible Church, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 36)
    - Family Protection Scoreboard, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 37)
    - Faith Tabernacle of Prayer for All People, Inc, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 38)
    - The Family Recognition Committee Inc., 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 39)
    - Far northeast-Southeast Council, Inc, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 40)
    - Far Southeast Community Organization, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 41)
    - Farmers' Market, 1984; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 42)
    - Farragut Development Company, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 43)
    - Federation of Citizens Associations, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 44)
    - Festival Development Cor., 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 45)
    - Fifteenth St. Citizens' Association, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 70, Folder 46)
    - Fifteenth St. Presbytherian Church, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Food and Allied Service Trades, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Food and Beverage Union, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - For Baby's Sake, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - For Love of Children, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Franklin Square Association, Inc, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - The Frederick Douglas Improvement Council, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Friends for Education, Inc., 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Friends of the DC Public Library, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Friends of St. Elizabeths, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Friendship House, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Friendship House Association, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Friendship Neighborhood Coalition, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Friends of Prividence Park, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Furs Unlimited, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Futures Fund & Fellowship Foundation, Inc, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Future View Inc, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - The Galatians Baptist Church, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Galilee Baptist Church, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - The Gallup Organization, Inc., 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Gannett CO., Inc., 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Gap Community Child Care Center, Inc., 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Gap Day Community Child Care Center, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Garden Memorial Presbyterian, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - Gay Activists Alliance, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - Geico, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 26)
    - George Washington University, undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 27)
    - Georgetown Admissions Ambassadors Program, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 28)
    - Georgetown School of Science and Arts, LTD., 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 29)
    - Georgetown University Medical Center, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 30)
    - Gertrude Stein Democratic Club, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 31)
    - Giant Food Inc., 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 32)
    - Girl Scouts, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 33)
    - Golden Age Key Club, 1984; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 34)
    - Government Employees Insurance Company, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 35)
    - Grace Memorial Church, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 36)
    - Grant Park Care Center, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 37)
    - Greater Morning Star Pentecostal Church, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 38)
    - Greater Mt. Calvary Baptist Church, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 39)
    - Greater Mt. Pisgah Baptist Church, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 40)
    - The Greater Southeast Community Hospital Foundation, Inc., 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 41)
    - Greater Washington Americans for Democratic Action, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 71, Folder 42)
    - Greater Washington Board of Trade, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Greater Washington Area NBA, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Greater Washington Council of Churches, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Greater Washington Grape Boycott Support Committee, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Greater Washington / Md. Service Station & Auto Repair Assoc., 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Greater Washington Petroleum Committee, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Greater Washington Research Center, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Greater Washington Society for Clinical Social Works, Inc., 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Greenleaf Senior Citizens Dwellings, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Greyhound, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Group Insurance Administration, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Hadley Memorial Hospital, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Hagen-Dazs, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Halt (American for Legal Reform), 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Happy Daze Luxury Charters, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Harbour Square, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Harlequin Dinner Theatre, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Harvard University, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Harvey Memorial Baptist Church, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Harvest Mission Church, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Health Care Access Protection Coalition, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Hechinger, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Hechts, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Helen Carey Real Estate, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - Hemlock Society of the National Capital, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - Herbert Rubenstein and Associates, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - Historic First Baptist Church of Georgetown, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 27)
    - Holy Comforter - Saint Cyprian's, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 28)
    - Holy Temple Church of Christ, Inc., 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 29)
    - Holly Name Church, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 30)
    - Horning Brothers Real Estate, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 31)
    - Hotel Association of Washington DC, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 32)
    - Hotel & Restuarant Employees Local, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 33)
    - House of Laureze, Inc., 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 34)
    - House of Ruth Friends, 1985; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 35)
    - Housing Now!, 1989; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 36)
    - Housing Opportunities for Women, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 37)
    - Howard University, 1990; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 38)
    - Hygolet Toilet, Inc., 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 39)
    - IBM, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 40)
    - Imprint Products, 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 41)
    - Industrial Bank of Washington, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - International Developers Inc., 1988; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Independent Funeral Directors Assoc., 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Independent Living for Handicapped, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Innovative Design & Development, 1987; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Institutional Buyers Mart Inc, Undated; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Interested Southeast Parents Association, 1986; Series 4 subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 7)